# ALEXANDER EDWARDIO

# IT Developer

### **PROFILE**



My name is Alexander Edwardio. I'm 27 years old who currently looking for a job that related to my majors at Binus University. I have a bachelor degree in Computer Science. Had been working at Bank Sinarmas and got a job as IT Developer. After my employment ended as IT Developer, I join many kind of online course related to Computer Science and helping my family business to grow and improve. I have strong technical skills as well as my interpersonal skills. I like learning something new. I am eager to be challenged in order to grow and improve my communication and professional IT skills gained through previous experiences in the IT sector.

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

#### **Address**

Grogol Petamburan DKI Jakarta, 11460 Indonesia

#### **Phone**

08998253588

#### **Email**

alexanderedwardio14@gmail.com

#### **DOB**

14 May 1995

#### **SKILLS**

SQL

Python

C#

Java

HTML / CSS / Javascript

### **LANGUAGE**

Bahasa English

# **LINKS**

linkedin.com/in/alexander-edwardio alexanderedwardio14.github.io

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## IT Developer at PT Bank Sinarmas Tbk, Jakarta Barat

October 2017 - September 2020

- Participated with clients in discussion meetings.
- Worked closely with other team members in such tasks as troubleshooting and debugging.
- Resolved system test and validation problems to provide normal program functioning.
- Participated in design and planning exercises for future software rollouts.
- Develop and maintain a web based application for customer service using PEGASystem.

#### Entrepreneur at NONA Homemade, Jakarta Barat

September 2020 - Present

- Implemented process improvement to shape organizational culture, optimize procedures for higher efficiency and help NONA Homemade evolve and grow.
- Created and updated company digital presence to enhance marketing through optimized social media profiles.
- Tasted or smelled foods or beverages to evaluate whether flavors met specifications or to select samples with specific characteristics.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Science (GPA: 3.1), Bina Nusantara University, Jakarta Barat September 2013 - August 2017

My major is Computer Science at Binus University with specialization in Database. I choose Computer Science because i like solving problems and want to make money from what i like.

# **INTERNSHIP**

#### Web Developer at PT. Bali Auto, Jakarta Pusat

April 2016 - June 2016

Me and my friends got a project from our lecturer for develop a program or application that help other people. We working as web developer at PT Bali Auto. PT Bali Auto is a company that sell a vehicle such as car and motorbike. At Bali Auto, we develop a web database application to help the owner. Application that we develop is for record income and outcome for selling and buying a vehicle.